TV를 볼 때에는 방을 밝게 하고 TV에서 떨어져서 봅시다.
When you're watching television, be sure to keep your room bright and keep distance from the TV!
강하게... 곱게...
Strong and gentle...
우리는 SUPER GUYS
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
메다로트: 혼
Medarot: Spirits
(Medarotto Damashī)
무적의 히로야!!
We are matchless heroes!!
태어난 그 순간이
The very moment of being born
기적을 부르는 사랑과 정의
It is the love and justice calling for a miracle
멀리 떨어져 있어도
Even when separated by distance
믿는 불꽃의 혼
The spirit of flame believes in each other
흘러라 빛나는 땀!
Flow! Sparkling sweat!
불타는 혼
Burning spirit!
둘이서라면 무한의 파워!
When there are two, infinite power shows itself!
꿈이여 펼쳐져라!
Let dreams unfold!
우리는 SUPER GUYS!
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
고고한 히로야!!
We are lonely yet proud heroes!!
메타비! 레클리스 모드!
Metabee! Reckless Mode!
좋아!
Got it!
메타비! 변속해!
Metabee! Change speed!
해 볼게!
I'll try!
메타비?
Metabee?
괜찮아, 메타비?
Are you okay, Metabee?
파워가 너무 강해...
I'm too strong...
틀렸어.
No.
금지된 싸움!
Prohibited Battle!
(en: Fighting Temptation)
메타비의 주행 상황을 슬로 모션으로 봐 보자.
Let's take a look at Metabee's driving in slow motion.
레클리스 모드가 되고 나서부터.
When he changed into Reckless Mode...
배틀 모드에서의 속도도 조금 모자라고, 레클리스 모드로 변형한 이후에도 가속이 전혀 안 되어 있어.
His speed in Battle Mode is lacking, and he isn't accelerating at all even in Reckless Mode.
어떻게 된 거에요, 나에 씨?
What's going on here, Ms. Nae?
결론부터 먼저 말하면 틴펫하고 새 파트가 완전히 호환되지 않아.
The conclusion is that his tinpet and new parts aren't not fully compatible.
허니? S자 커브까지 돌려 봐.
Honey? Go to S-curve scene.
네.
Got it.
여기부터 가속을 받았을 때의 흔들림을 감당하지 못했어.
He failed to withstand the shake from the acceleration.
그래도 이 전에 긴카이인가 하는 놈의 뉴 타입 메다로트를 쓰러뜨렸을 때는 아무것도 아니었는데 이상하네...
But it was nothing when he took down the new type Medarot of that Ginkai guy. It's weird.
그건 그냥 운이 좋았을 뿐이야. 상대가 스피드 타입 메다로트라면 졌을 거야.
That was a pure luck. If the opponent was a speed-type Medarot, he probably has lost.
내가 진다고? 농담 마!
I lose? No way!
상대는 지금까지 싸워 온 메다로트 사의 메다로트가 아니야.
The opponent is not Medarot that is made by Medarot Company as you know.
뭐, 뭐라고?
W- what?
무슨 소리야? 메다로트는 메다로트 사가 만든 거 아니야?
What are you talking about? Isn't Medarot Company making Medarot?
그래.
Right.
중장비. 대량의 탄약. 강화 장갑.
Heavily armed. Massive ammo. Strengthened armors.
그리고 규칙 위반.
And going aginst the rules.
로보틀을 걸어온 긴카이라는 소년.
That Ginkai boy who asked you for a Robattle.
메다로트 사의 메다로트 정신에서 크게 떨어져 있어.
He's far off from the spirit of Medarot of Medarot Company.
메다로트 사와 다른 생각을 가지고 만들어진 메다로트.
The Medarots that are made with a different way of thinking.
그걸 그 아이는 어디서 손에 넣었을까?
Where did that boy get that?
정말 너무 위험한 것 같아. 상관하지 않는 게 좋아.
They seem to be too dangerous. You'd better not be involved with them.
나에 씨...
Ms. Nae...
나에 씨는 대체 누구에요?
Who are you, Ms. Nae?
어?
Huh?
그냥 잡화상이랬잖아.
I told you I'm just a sundries dealer.
그냥 잡화상치고는 너무 자세해요.
You know too much to be just an everyday sundries dealer.
응, 응!
Yeah, yeah!
그래? 사실은 말야, 나는 메다로트 사의 개발부에서 일했었어.
You think so? To tell you the truth, I worked in product development division of Medarot Company.
아하! 그래서 잘 알고 있구나!
Oh! That's why you knew a lot!
그래도 말이에요, 메다로트 사의 개발부라고 하면 아이들이 취직하고 싶은 회사 제일 아니에요?
But, isn't the development division of Medarot Company the place that children most want to be employed?
왜 관뒀어요?
Why did you quit?
사무실에 박혀서 일하는 것보다는 아이들하고 메다로트들이 우정과 신뢰를 쌓으며
Instead of working in an office, I wanted to see children and Medarots growing up
로보틀을 통해 성장하는 모습을 내 눈으로 직접 보고 싶어서 말야.
via Robattles, accumulating friendship and trust.
그리고 그걸 돕고 싶어서일까.
And I wanted to help that.
예쁘다. 내 타입이야.
She's pretty. She's my type.
어때? 메타비 새 파트를 잠깐 나한테 맡기지 않을래?
Hey, would you like to let me take care of Metabee's new parts for a short time?
어?
Huh?
48시간 이내에 메타비의 틴펫하고 새 파트가 잘 맞게 만들어 볼게.
I'll make Metabee's Tinpet and new parts compatible enough.
나, 나에 씨가 내 바디의 이런 곳도 저런 곳도 만지작거린다고 한다면, 기쁘게!
I- if Ms. Nae is touching these parts and those parts of my body... happily!
너 야한 생각 하니?
Are you thinking about something lewd?
시꺼! 태클걸지 마!
Shut up! Don't riposte!
그렇다면.
Well then.
보디가 없으니 정말 꼬라지 한번 하고는!
Without his body, he looks extremely good!
꺼져!
Get lost!
잇키 군? 새 파트를 바로잡을 동안 옛날 파트 끼워 줘.
Ikki? During I repair the new parts, give him the old parts.
네! 구 파트, 전송!
Yes! Transfer old parts!
이 쪽이 딱이야.
This feels perfect.
걱정 마. 새 파트도 딱이 되도록 개조해서
Don't worry. I'll modify your new parts so that you feel perfect with the new parts too,
모레 점심 12시까지 집에 가져다 줄게.
and I'll take it to your home by 12'o clock the day after tomorrow.
그럼 저흰 여기서 실례할게요!
We'll be going by now!
안녕히!
Bye-bye!
-잠깐.
-어?
-Wait.
-Huh?
수리가 끝날 때까지는 절대 긴카이의 메다로트하고 싸우면 안 돼.
Until the repair is done, you must not fight against Ginkai's Medarot.
음... 그래도 말이죠...
Uh... but you know...
절대 안 돼. 여기서 약속해.
You must not. Promise me right now, right here.
잠깐만! 로보틀을 걸어 왔으면 상대하는 게 내 원칙이니까...
Just a moment! My policy is to face whoever asks me for a Robattle...
-그치?
-어.
-Isn't it true?
-Yeah.
그럼 이렇게 하자. 만약 약속을 지킨다면,
Then let me make a proposal. If you keep the promise,
둘이 원하는 것이라면 이런 것이든 저런 것이든 해줄테니까.
I'll do whatever you two wants, even if it's this or that.
이런 것이라던가...
Maybe this...
or this...
약속할게요!
We're promising!
너희들 말야...
You guys have problems...
잇키 군? 메타비?
Ikki? Metabee?
오른손 내봐.
Show me your right hands.
네.
Here.
긴카이 녀석하고 싸우게 된다면 이 약속의 증표를 보고 견뎌.
If you happen to fight against Ginkai, look at this sign of promise and endure.
알겠어?
Got it?
네! 견딜게요!
Yeah! We'll endure!
이건 두목이 기뻐하겠어!
This will make my boss happy!
정말 이 큰 저택이 그 코쿠류라는 놈 집이야?
Are you saying that this big residence is that Kokuryu guy's house?
틀림없어요. 긴카이하고 같이 들어가는 걸 이 눈으로 봤어요.
No doubt about it. I saw him getting into with Ginkai with my own eyes.
음, 저 만큼 파트나 탄알을 막 쓰니까 부자라고는 생각했는데...
Well, I did know that he must be a rich, to be able to use parts and bullets that much...
설마 저렇게까지 부자일 줄이야...
But I didn't know he was a billionaire...
코쿠류 도련님. 메다로트의 새 파트와 탄약 류를 가지고 찾아왔습니다.
Young master Kokuryu, we're here with new Medarot parts and a variety of bullets.
수고했어. 문을 열게.
Good job. I'll open the door.
들었어? 카가미야마.
Did you hear, Kagamiyama?
예. 저 컨테이너 전부가 메다로트의 파트와 탄약이라니.
Yeah. All those containers are full of Medarot parts and bullets...
더 오는 거야?!
Is there an end to that?!
두목! 굿 뉴스, 굿 뉴스!
Boss! Good news! Good news!
뭐야.
What is it?
사실은...
It's...
우리에게도 행운이 찾아왔나 보구나.
It seems that a luck is here for us, too.
이, 이게 제 3 응접실!
T- this is the 3rd reception room!
제 1이나 2 응접실이라면 더 호화스럽겠죠?!
The 1st or 2nd reception room must be even more luxury!
두목!
Boss!
주눅들 거 없어. 데이트하면 어때, 나처럼?
There's nothing to be shocked. How about a date with him, like me?
잘 왔어.
Welcome.
이건 이건 코쿠류 씨! 실례합니다! 이야, 훌륭한 방이네요!
This must be Mr. Kokuryu! Excuse me! This really is an excellent room!
인사는 됐어. 어쨌든, 메타비에 관해서 들은 정보가 뭐야?
Forget about greetings. What's that information that you've heard about Metabee?
공짜일 리가.
It's not for free.
돈 원해?
Do you want money?
돈이 아니에요.
It's not money.
바로 말하면, 새 파트.
To put to the point, a new part.
그래?
Is that so?
내 페퍼캣에게 고전류 배터리를 주면 알려 줄게요.
If you give my Peppercat a high output battery, then I'll tell you.
이 자식!
You brat!
뻔뻔스러운 것에도 정도가 있지!
Don't you know what's a shame?!
뭐, 됐어. 조건대로 할게.
Well, it's alright. I'll do as you told.
긴카이, 오늘 입고된 파트 가지고 와.
Ginkai, take the part that came in today here.
어? 어.
Huh? Duh.
좋아!
It worked!
두목, 해 냈네요! 지금까지의 배터리보다 300배나 출력이 높다니 대단해요!
Boss, you did it! That battery has 300 times the output of the one you've been using!
그렇게 간단히 될 거라고는 생각도 못 했어.
I never thought it'd work that easily.
이걸로 코쿠류가 메타비를 쓰러뜨리기만 한다면 드디어 두목의 천하네요!
If Kokuryu manages to take Metabee down by this, the world is in your hands, boss!
그런 거지! 서둘러서 페퍼캣에게 달자!
That's right. Let's hurry and put it on Peppercat!
코쿠류, 나라면 새 파트 안 주고 힘으로 정보를 알아냈겠다.
Kokuryu, if I was you, I'd use force to make them spit it out.
쟤들한테 새 파트를 주어 보았자 제대로 못 쓸 거야. 감전되어서 부서지는 게 함정이지.
They won't use the new part I gave them. It'll receive an electric shock and break down.
어, 너, 그거 알고 있었다면 일부러?
Hey, if you knew that, then were you on purpose?
우, 웃고 있어! 무서운 놈...
H- he's laughing! What a scary guy...
페퍼캣! 왜 그래!
Peppercat! What's wrong?!
모, 몸이 마비되어요!
M- my body is getting numb!
페퍼캣!
Peppercat!
두목...
Boss...
숙여! 당장!
Get down! Now!
네, 네이팜?
N- Napalm?
누구냐!
Who's there?!
TND형 탱크댕크
TND Type Tankdank
긴카이! 너!
Ginkai! You!
코쿠류, 얘냬들이 잇키하고 메타비다.
Kokuryu, these are Ikki and Metabee.
처음 보네, 잇키 군, 메타비.
Nice to meet you, Ikki and Metabee.
-코쿠류?
-그거, 니 메다로트냐?
-Kokuryu?
-Is that your Medarot?
새 파트를 수리하고 있댔지?
You were repairing your new parts, right?
왜, 왜 알고 있어!
W- why do you know that?!
키쿠히메인가 하는 놈이 직접 알려주러 왔어.
Someone named Kikuhime came to tell us that.
왜 네가 구 파트 그대로인지도 말이지!
Including why are you using your old parts, that is!
젠장, 키쿠히메 놈! 쓸데없는 짓을!
Damn that Kikuhime! How dare she do that?!
그 동안 긴카이의 건 데스페라도를 파괴해 줘서 고마워.
Thank you for destroying Ginkai's Gun Desperado back then.
오늘은 배로 갚아 줄게.
I'll pay that back in multiple today
뭐라?!
What?!
난 약한 상대를 적당히 대한다거나 하지 않으니까.
I don't treat whoever's weak adequately.
목숨을 끊어 줄게.
I'll cut your breathe.
입에서 나오는 거라고 죄다 말이라고 알고 있나 보지?!
Do you think whatever comes out from your mouth makes sense?!
메타비! 갚아 주자!
Metabee! Let's pay that back!
당연하지!
Of course!
어?
Huh?
승부.
A match.
시러.
Nah.
뭐?
What?
안됐지만 우린 수리가 끝날 때까지 싸우지 않기로 나에 씨한테 약속했거든!
Too bad for you, but we promised Ms. Nae not to fight until the repair is done!
약속을 지키면 나에 씨가 이런 것도 그런 것도 해 줄 거야!
If I keep the promise, Ms. Nae will do this thing and that thing to me!
뭔 소리야, 너희들?
What are you talking about, you guys?
어쨌든 그런 줄 알아, 임마!
That's all about it!
미안하지만!
Excuse us!
안녕!
See ya!
야, 야, 임마! 멈춰!
H- h- hey! Stop!
어이, 코쿠류! 왜 안 쫒아?
Hey, Kokuryu! Why aren't you chasing them?
(오다 노부나가: 울지 않으면 죽여버릴 터이니 두견새야
도요토미 히데요시: 울지 않으면 울려 보이마 두견새야
도쿠가와 이에야스: 울지 않으면 울 때까지 기다리마 두견새야)
([Loser] Oda Nobunaga: Dear cuckoo, I will kill you if you don't chirp
[Loser] Toyotomi Hideyoshi: Dear cuckoo, I will make you chirp if you don't
[Winner] Tokugawa Ieyasu: Dear cuckoo, I will wait until you chirp)
"울지 않으면 울려 보이마 두견새야"라는 말도 있잖아.
There is a saying "Dear cuckoo, I will make you chirp if you don't," you know.
탱크댕크, 가라!
Tankdank, go!
-힘의 차원이 달라!
-포기할게!
-Their power is on the different level!
-We give up!
그, 그만둬! 메다로트의 혼을 부수지 마!
S- stop it! Don't destroy the spirits of Medarots!
메달까지 부수다니 과해!
Destroying the medals is too much!
저건 너무했다.
That's too much.
이런 건 로보틀 아니야.
This is not a Robattle.
더러워!
That's dirty!
닥쳐! 개소리밖에 못 하는 놈들!
Shut up, you naysayers!
우리는 말야, 텐료 잇키와 메타비가 싸울 때까지 이 마을 안의 모든 메다로트를 전부 쳐부수겠다!
We will destroy all the Medarots in this village until Tenryo Ikki and Metabee fight us!
다음에 탱크댕크의 희생자가 되고 싶은 건 누구야?
Who wants to be the next victim of Tankdank?
내, 내 마지 스페셜이!
M- my True Special!
메달까지 부수다니 저 놈들 용서할 수 없어!
They even destroyed the medal! I can't forgive them!
관둬, 메타비!
Stop, Metabee!
놔, 잇키!
Let me go, Ikki!
나에 씨하고 약속은 어쩌고?
What about the promise with Ms. Nae?
그런 거, 지키고 있을 때가 아냐!
This is no time to protect that!
지금 장착하고 있는 오래된 파트라면 이길 수 있을 리가 없어!
With the old parts you're now using, you cannot win!
시꺼! 이대로 죄도 없는 메다로트가 파괴당해도, 너 아무것도 못 느끼냐, 이 겁쟁아!
Shut up! Can't you feel anything, when Medarots without any fault get destroyed one after another, you wimp?!
거, 겁쟁이라고?! 그래, 알겠다! 해 보자!
W- wimp, you say?! Well then! Let's fight!
잇키!
Ikki!
허니!
Honey!
나에 씨의 말을 전하러 왔어.
I'm here to tell what Ms. Nae told.
지금 중요한 건 약속을 지키는 것. 저들의 목적은 메타비 씨의 메달을 파괴하는 거야.
What's important now is keeping the promise. Their objective is to destroy your medla, Mr. Metabee.
그래도...
But...
그 레어 메달 속에는 누가 축적해 온 전투 노하우 외에, 더 소중한 게 모여 있잖아?
In your Rare Medal, don't you have something more valuable then battle techniques?
더 소중한 거?
Something more valuable?
둘의 우정과 신뢰.
The friendship and trust between you two.
우리...
Our...
그런 소중한 것까지 부서져도 좋아?
Is it okay, even if that gets destroyed along?
허니가 말하는 대로야. 내일 정오까지 쓰라려도 참아.
Just as Honey said. It will be painful, but endure it until tomorrow's noon.
그러지 못할 거야.
You won't.
코, 코쿠류!
K- Kokuryu!
가라, 탱크댕크!
Go, Tankdank!
이랴!
Come face me!
메타비!
Metabee!
네이팜으로 공격해.
Use napalm to attack them.
좋아! 가위바위-
Well! Rock-scissor-
보!
Paper!
저기나 봐라!
That way!
여기!
There!
탱크댕크! 뭐 하니?
Tankdank! What are you doing?
이번엔 도망가지 못할 거야. 고리로더, 전송.
You're not getting away this time. Transfer Goriroader.
쫒아!
Chase!
탄환을 전송했어!
He transferred bullets!
공격해 온다!
They're attacking us!
맡겨.
Leave it to me.
방해꾼은 꺼져라!
Hindrance be lost!
새 바디가 오면 배로 해서 갚아 주겠어!
When I get the new body, I'll pay back in multiples!
나에 씨, 정오부터 아무것도 안 먹었어. 몸에 좋지 않아.
Ms. Nae, you didn't eat anything since noon. It's not good for your body.
메타비와 잇키가 약속을 지키며 견디고 있는데, 식사 따위는 할 수 없어.
Metabee and Ikki are bearing, keeping the promise. I don't have time for a meal.
1분이라도 빨리 완성해 보이겠어.
I'll do my best to finish this as soon as possible.
나에 씨...
Ms. Nae...
왜 집에서 안 기다리니?
Why aren't you waiting at your home?
미안해요. 메타비가 뭔 일이 있어도 막 가고 싶대서...
I'm sorry. Metabee wanted to get here so badly...
안절부절하지를 못했어! 그래서 파트는?
I couldn't sit still! So, what about the parts?
마지막 조정을 하고 있으니까, 10분 정도만 있으면 완성될 거야. 조금만 더 기다려.
I'm doing final adjustments. It'll take 10 minutes. Wait for a moment.
-좋아!
-이걸로 코쿠류한테 이길 수 있겠어!
-Yes!
-I'll be able to defeat Kokuryu by this!
과연 그럴까?
I wonder.
잇키 군 집에서 따라왔어.
We've followed you from your house, Ikki.
코쿠류!
Kokuryu!
탱크댕크, 파트가 완성되기 전에 메타비를 쳐부숴.
Tankdank, demolish Metabee before the parts arecomplete.
여긴 내게 맡기고 빨리 파트를 완성시켜!
Leave this to me and complete the parts as soon as possible!
허니! 알았어. 되는 대로 시간을 끌어 줘.
Honey! Got it. Try to buy some time as much as possible.
잇키 군, 메타비, 파트 옮기는 걸 도와줘. 바깥의 차에 옮겨 줘.
Ikki and Metabee, help me move the parts. Move them to the car outside.
탱크댕크, 어서 저 메다로트를 쓰러뜨리고 메타비를 부숴.
Tankdano, get rid of that Medarot and destroy Metabee right now.
더는 참을 수가 없어!
I can't stand this anymore!
메타비, 돌아와!
Metabee, come back!
질 거라는 걸 알아도 싸우지 않으면 안될 때도 있어!
Even if I know I will lose, there are times that I must fight!
잇키 군.
Ikki.
미안해요, 나에 씨. 우리...
I'm sorry, Ms. Nae. We...
막아도 소용 없나 보구나. 가. 그래도 이건 약속해.
I guess it's no use trying to stop you. Go. But promise me this.
내가 완성하기까지는 절대 지지 않는다고.
Until I finish this, you must not lose.
네.
Got it.
로보틀은 무기의 우열만이 승부를 가리는 게 아니야.
The superiority of weapons don't decide the outcome of a Robattle.
메다로터의 지혜와 메다로트의 팀워크야말로 최고의 무기야.
The wisdom of Medarotter and the teamwork with Medarot are the best weapons.
-가자, 메타비!
-좋아!
-Let's go, Metabee!
-Right!
역시 남자얘들이구나.
Boys will be boys.
서둘러야지.
I must hurry.
이랴!
I will face you!
소용 없다니까. 탱크댕크, 뒤로 돌아 들어가.
I said that it's no use. Tankdank, go to the back side.
반응탄으로 공격해, 메타비!
Attack it with Reactive Bullets, Metabee!
좋아!
Got it!
오른팔, 대미지 포인트 99.999. 서브머신건 사용 불능.
Right arm, damage point 99.999. Submachine Gun disabled.
일어나, 메타비! 노려진다! 달려!
Stand up, Metabee! You're being targeted! Run!
기회야! 접근해서 단숨에 공격해!
It's your chance! Approach and attack at once!
이게!
You bastard!
전송.
Transfer.
더러워!
That's dirty!
쏴!
Fire!
젠장! 리볼버도 앞으로 탄환이 두 발밖에 안 남아 있어! 이제 어째!
Damn it! I only have two bullets in my revolver! What should we do now?!
메타비.
Metabee...
로보틀은 무기의 우열만이 승부를 가리는 게 아니야.
The superiority of weapons don't decide the outcome of a Robattle.
메다로터의 지혜와 메다로트의 팀워크야말로 최고의 무기야.
The wisdom of Medarotter and the teamwork with Medarot are the best weapons.
그래! 이길 수는 없어도 무승부는 낼 수 있겠어!
That's it! While we can't win, we can at least end in a draw!
메타비! 리볼버를 쏴! 여길 조준해!
Metabee! Use your revolver! Shoot at these points!
알았어!
Got it!
끝장내, 탱크댕크!
Finish this, Tankdank!
먹어라!
Take this!
머리 및 왼팔, 기능 정지.
Head and left arm parts stopped working.
뭐?
What?
탱크댕크, 육탄전으로 넘어가!
Tankdank, enter hand-to-hand combat!
발도 안 움직여?
Are the legs also not working?
못 움직이면 승부는 비긴 거네.
If neither can move, it's a tie.
나에 씨!
Ms. Nae!
수리 완료했어.
The repair is done.
좋아!
Yeah!
코쿠류 군. 끝장내고 싶으면 따라와. 거기서 승부를 봐.
Kokuryu. If you want to settle this, follow me, and settles this there.
바라던 바야.
That's what I wanted.
어?
Huh?
관절의 틈에 탄환을 박아서 움직이지 못하게 막았다니, 생각보다 꽤 하는구나.
To put bullets into the gap at joints, they do better than I expected.
잇키 군.
Ikki.
메타비! 전송!
Metabee! Transfer!
왠지 파워가 넘쳐흘러!
Power is overflowing in my body!
수리했다고 해 보았자, 결국 메다로트 사제 메다로트잖아.
Even if it have gone through repairs, it's still a product of Medarot Company.
간단히 쳐부숴 줄게.
I'll destroy him easily enough.
가라, 탱크댕크!
Go, Tankdank!
몸이 가볍게 느껴져! 이거라면 되겠어!
My body is lighter than ever! This will do perfectly!
이랴!
Take this!
뭐야?
What?
서브머신건도 힘이 올라갔어!
Submachine Gun has also been improved!
레클리스 모드!
Reckless Mode!
간다!
Here I go!
노멀 모드! 점프! 바리스터, 발사!
Normal Mode! Jump! Use Ballister!
끝장이다!
Finisher!
해냈어!
We did it!
기뻐하는 것도 지금뿐이야. 탱크댕크는 내 콜렉션에서 제일 약한 메다로트야.
You won't be laughing for long. Tankdank is the weakest Medarot among my collection.
다음에는 이렇게 되지 않을 거야.
This won't happen next time.
부탁드려요! 제... 제 페퍼캣을 고쳐 주세요!
I beg you! Please... please repair my Peppercat!
임마! 코쿠류한테 부탁한 주제에 잘도 그런 소리가 나오겠다!
Hey! How can you ask us, when you asked Kokuryu for a favor?!
배신자 놈! 돌아가라, 돌아가!
You traitor! Go back, go back!
두목, 다른 잡화상에 가요.
Boss, let's go to an other sundries shop.
잠깐. 고쳐 줄게.
Stop. I'll repair.
정말이에요?
Really?!
-어.
-나에 씨!
-Yeah.
-Ms. Nae!
메다로트를 마음 깊이 사랑하는 자라면 누구라도 내게는 손님이야.
Whoever loves Medarots from the deep of one's mind is my customer.
자, 줘 봐.
You can give her to me.
가, 감사합니다!
T- thank you so much!
감사합니다!
Thank you so much!
점점 아름답다!
She's getting more beautiful!
점점 취향이야!
She's so my type!
아침은 싫어하지만 어느 날 돌연
Mornings are not my favorite, but someday on a sudden
자명종 울리기 전에 일어났어
I woke up before my alarm clock rings
내 가슴이 메어지게 괴로워
My wringing heart is so troubled
슬픈 만큼 당신은 연상의 사람
As much as I'm sad, you are older than me
쭉 보고 있어도 닿지 않아
Gazing at you isn't getting me through
키하고 하트
Height and heart
빛나는 미소는
Is the shining smile
우러러 볼 뿐만인 태양?
nothing more than a sun that I admire?
Don't mind 신경쓰지 마
Don't mind, don't make it let you down
My girl 쏘아올리기 전에
To my girl, before you make a dash,
Fight mind 무기력함에 져 버린다면
have a fighting mindset! If you lose to timorousness,
사랑은 잡을 수 없어
you cannot catch the love
차회예고
Preview for Next Episode
잇키와 메타비에게 뜻하지 않게 계속 연패당한 코쿠류는 공포의 가이로트 군단을 투입,
After being consecutively defeated by Ikki and Metabee, Kokuryu deployed fearful Gairot Force,
잇키와 메타비에게 달라붙은 악마의 칼날.
and the blade of demon are getting closer to Ikki and Metabee.
그 때, 소나기와 함께 수수께끼의 메다로터 등장.
At that moment, a mysterious Medarotter has appeared with a shower.
도쿠스의 포바이스가 빛난다.
Dorcus' Forvice is shining.
과연 그 자는 적인가 아군인가?
Is that guy their enemy or friend?
코쿠류가 노리는 건 대체 어디에 있는가?
Where is the thing Kokuryu's aiming at?
메다로트 혼의 다음 이야기! 수수께끼의 도쿠스 사용자
Next time on Medarot: Spirits! Mysterious Dorcus Wielder
타올라라, 뜨거운 혼이여!
Let the hot spirit burn up!